Guide to the J. Walter Thompson Company. Account Files, 1885-2008 and undated, bulk 1920-1995 RL.00658
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- U.S. Sprint, 1980-2000 and undated, 60 boxes
  - General
    - [Organizing for local market opportunities, 1997: Removed to Restricted Materials Box SR56.], 3 folders (Box SR28)
    - [Orientation for Sprint Ltd consumer and small business markets, 1998: Removed to Restricted Materials Box SR56.] (Box SR28)
    - Outage plan of attack, 1992 (Box SR28)
    - Payback analyses, 1986 (Box SR28)
    - Performance analysis, 1983-1986, 4 folders (Box SR28)
    - Performance evaluation forms and policy, 1989 (Box SR29)
    - Pin Money, 1987 (Box SR29)
    - Planning audit, 1981 (Box SR29)
    - Planning, 1982-1989, 4 folders (Box SR29)
    - Pocket campaign acetates,, undated (Box SR29)
    - Post-buy analysis, 1982 (Box SR29)
    - Prepaid Fon Card advertising strategy, 1993 (Box SR29)
    - Pre-production meeting, 1983 (Box SR29)
    - Present for US Sprint, 1989 (Box SR29)
    - Presentation binder, 1983-1984, 3 folders (Box SR29)
    - Presentation to 4-A, 1990 (Box SR29)
    - [Presentation: Building the Sprint Brand, 1998: Moved to Restricted Materials Box SR56] (Box SR29)
    - [Presentation: Integrated Advertising Support (NFL sponsorship), 1996: Moved to Restricted Materials Box SR56] (Box SR29)
    - Presentation: J. Walter Thompson strategic plan,, undated (Box SR29)
    - Presentation: U.S. carrier country direct, 1994 (Box SR29)
    - Pre-subscription creative, 1984 (Box SR30)
    - Pre-subscription focus group, 1984 (Box SR30)
    - Pre-subscription research, 1984 (Box SR30)
    - Pre-subscription T-Plan, 1984 (Box SR30)
    - Print advertising, 1982-1988, 6 folders (Box SR30)
    - Print estimates, 1983, 1-4 of 5 folders (Box SR30)
    - Print estimates, 1983, 5 of 5 folders (Box SR31)
    - Print schedule 2nd half, 1987 (Box SR31)
    - Pricing, 1987, 2 folders (Box SR31)
    - Product Movers cooperative couponing, 1985 (Box SR31)
    - Production, 1992 (Box SR31)
    - Promotion, 1984-1985, 2 folders (Box SR31)
    - Promotion planning, 1986 (Box SR31)
    - Promotions update, 1990 (Box SR31)
    - Publication, Advertising 2000 A.D., Hunter Madsen, 1994 (Box SR31)
    - Publication, The Future of the Web, 1995 (Box SR31)
    - Publication: Yankelovich Pop Monitor, How Popular Culture Defines American Consumers, 1995 (Box SR31)
    - [Q4 1997 creative presentations: Short calls- satisfaction, 1997: Removed to Restricted Materials Box SR56.] (Box SR31)
    - Qualitative assessment of long distance business, 1984 (Box SR31)
    - Radio advertising, 1983, 1988, 2 folders (Box SR31)
    - Ralph Sherman introduction, 1983 (Box SR31)
    - Relaunching U.S Sprint, 1988 (Box SR32)
    - Repositioning field sales, 1984 (Box SR32)
    - Residence customer profile study, 1983 (Box SR32)
    - Response marketing network presentation, 1985 (Box SR32)
    - Review of Sprint Marketing Communications Activities, 1995 (Box SR32)
    - Revised competitive deck, 1993 (Box SR32)
    - Roll-out costs, 1981 (Box SR32)
    - Roll-out List recommendations, 1981 (Box SR32)
    - Sales, 1983 (Box SR32)
    - Sales code history, 1983, 2 folders (Box SR32)
    - Sales forecasting, 1984 (Box SR32)
    - Sales promotion, 1984 (Box SR32)
    - Satchel Page print 10/20 Wall Street Journal, 1987 (Box SR32)
    - Sell-Intuit, 1994 (Box SR32)
    - [Selling Sprint in the new telecommunications market, 1996: Removed to Restricted Materials Box SR57.], 2 folders (Box SR32)
    - Sherry Carniglia chronological file, 1987, 4 folders (Box SR33)
    - Signature study, 1983 (Box SR33)
    - Simon, Susan chronological file, 1982, 2 folders (Box SR33)
    - Smash Success print, 1987 (Box SR33)
    - Solidifying direction for the 1992 Sprint advertising plan, 1991 (Box SR33)
    - Southern Pacific Communications, 1980-1981 (Box SR33)
    - Space releases, 1982 (Box SR33)
    - Speeches
      - Chris Jones' Rome speech, 1995 (Box SR33)
      - Peter Schweitzer Rome Senior Partners conference, 1995 (Box SR33)
      - William Eccleshare The Strategic Plan, 1995 (Box SR33)
      - William Eccleshare The Strategic Plan making it happen, 1995 (Box SR33)
    - Spots--Sprint presubscription order tracking system, 1984 (Box SR33)
    - Sprint 800: Capitalizing on the window of opportunity, 1992 (Box SR33)
    - Sprint action plan, 1992 (Box SR33)
    - Sprint Advertising Academy, 1994-1995, 2 folders (Box SR33)
    - [Sprint Advertising Academy, 1996: Removed to Restricted Materials Box SR57.], 2 folders (Box SR34)
    - Sprint backgrounder, 1991 (Box SR34)
    - [Sprint brand identity standards, 1996: Removed to Restricted Materials Box SR57.] (Box SR34)
    - Sprint brand image, 1993 (Box SR34)
    - [Sprint college client meeting, 1997: Removed to Restricted Materials Box SR58.] (Box SR34)
    - Sprint competitive advertising overview, 1993 (Box SR34)
    - Sprint corporate 1994 legitimacy plan, 1994 (Box SR34)
    - Sprint corporate advertising 1996 Media budget analysis, 1995 (Box SR34)
    - Sprint corporate advertising recommendation, 1993 (Box SR34)
    - Sprint corporate image positioning research, 1992 (Box SR34)
    - Sprint coverage guide, 1984 (Box SR34)
    - Sprint CRP presentation, 1993 (Box SR34)
    - Sprint/CSG project Pivo creative presentation, 1993 (Box SR34)
    - Sprint and Education: A Partnership for the future, 1991 (Box SR34)
    - Sprint international access 1994 competitive review, 1995 (Box SR34)
    - Sprint international briefing, 1992 (Box SR34)
    - Sprint international sample advertising, 1995 (Box SR34)
    - [Sprint Internet Passport, 1996: Removed to Restricted Materials Box SR58.] (Box SR34)
    - Sprint-KCET partnership, 1987-1988 (Box SR34)
    - [Sprint-Lucas Films strategic partnership, 1997: Removed to Restricted Materials Box SR58.] (Box SR35)
    - Sprint product guide, 1993 (Box SR35)
    - [Sprint Sense brand review, 1997: Removed to Restricted Materials Box SR58.], 2 folders (Box SR35)
    - [Sprint Sense evolution, 1997: Removed to Restricted Materials Box SR58.], 2 folders (Box SR35)
    - Sprint service guarantee, 1989-1990 (Box SR35)
    - Sprint soccer update meeting, 1993 (Box SR35)
    - Sprint/Telecom merger factbook, 1986 (Box SR35)
    - Sprint vs MCI 1st quarter results, 1984 (Box SR35)
    - Status: Corporate image team, 1993 (Box SR35)
    - Stephen Kelly Awards, 1986 (Box SR35)
    - Steve Darland files
      - Advertising conference, 1992, 2 folders (Box SR35)
      - Alcatel information, 1993 (Box SR36)
      - Annual performance review, 1991-1992 (Box SR36)
      - Brag file, 1993 (Box SR36)
      - Candice survey, 1992 (Box SR36)
      - Corporate image team deck, 1993 (Box SR36)
      - Electronic data system information, 1992 (Box SR36)
      - General correspondence, 1992 (Box SR36)
      - General correspondence, 1993, 2 folders (Box SR36)
      - Housecalls information, 1990 (Box SR36)
      - Marketing segmentation objectives and measures file, 1989 (Box SR36)
      - Organization, 1993 (Box SR36)
      - Product presentation, 1993 (Box SR36)
      - Sprint branding, 1992 (Box SR36)
      - Sprint international, 1991-1993 (Box SR36)
      - Total Quality Management, 1993 (Box SR36)
    - Strategic and business progress vs. MCI, 1983 (Box SR37)
    - Strategic plan, 1993 (Box SR37)
    - Strategic planning meeting, 1983, 2 folders (Box SR37)
    - Strategic positioning, 1983 (Box SR37)
    - Strategic studies of Sprint market segments, 1988 (Box SR37)
    - Summary of Sprint bi-monthly marketing meeting, 1990 (Box SR37)
    - T-Plan, 1984, 2 folders (Box SR37)
    - [TCI Telephony new business meeting, 1996: Removed to Restricted Materials Box SR59.] (Box SR37)
    - Technology adoption process: Implications to CSG, 1993 (Box SR37)
    - Telecommunications clippings, 1987, 5 folders (Box SR38)
    - Telecommunications: The Decision-Makers (Dow Jones report), 1994 (Box SR38)
    - Television advertising, 1986-1988, 1-3 of 12 folders (Box SR38)
    - Television advertising, 1987, 4-12 of 12 folders (Box SR39)
    - Television spot, Wall Street, 1988 (Box SR39)
    - Television spots, 1993 (Box SR39)
    - Telly Awards, 1986 (Box SR39)
    - Tom Weigman's guidebook, 1993 (Box SR39)
    - Travel, 1991 (Box SR40)
    - TV Commercials from 1982 through August 1994, 1995, 2 folders (Box SR40)
    - United Telecom, 1989 (Box SR40)
    - Upsetting the Status Quo: Sprint's 1993 800-Service Advertising Campaign, 1992 (Box SR40)
    - U.S. Sprint
      - Advertising: Perspectives and possibilities, 1989 (Box SR40)
      - Articles, 1989 (Box SR40)
      - Clippings, 1989 (Box SR40)
      - Competitive advertisements and articles, 1989 (Box SR40)
      - House organs, 1988 (Box SR40)
      - Lexicon discs table of contents, 1984-1987 (Contains digital Media items) (Box SR40)
      - Market plan, 1988 (Box SR40)
      - Script binder, 1988, 4 folders (Box SR41)
      - UT/Sprint annual reports, 1986-1994, 3 folders (Box SR41)
    - Voice link, 1988 (Box SR41)
    - Weatherfon snipe, 1988 (Box SR41)
    - West division media/prod., 1987 (Box SR41)
    - Winter Olympics, 1991 (Box SR41)
    - World Cup soccer, 1994 (Box SR41)
    - Worldwide slide presentation, 1992 (Box SR42)
  - Business Sprint
    - General, 1982-1985, 2 folders (Box SR42)
    - Advertising, 1983 (Box SR42)
    - Communications briefing, 1983 (Box SR42)
    - Market plans, 1983 (Box SR42)
    - Media plan, 1983 (Box SR42)
    - Planning, 1984 (Box SR42)
    - Premium recommendation, 1983 (Box SR42)
    - Proposal for Exploratory Qualitative Research among Prime Prospect Decision Makers, 1983 (Box SR42)
    - Role of Advertising, 1983 (Box SR42)
    - Short Term program, 1983 (Box SR42)
  - Home Sprint
    - General, 1982-1983, 1-2 of 5 folders (Box SR42)
    - General (continued), 1982-1983, 3-5 of 5 folders (Box SR43)
    - Advertising report, 1983 (Box SR43)
    - Incremental plan, 1983 (Box SR43)
    - Marketing, 1984 (Box SR43)
    - Media plan, 1983-1984, 3 folders (Box SR43)
    - T-Plan, 1984 (Box SR43)
  - Research
    - General, 1981-1983, 2 folders (Box SR43)
    - Automatic dialing service market research study, 1983 (Box SR43)
    - Brand Image Tracking Study, 1993 (Box SR44)
    - Business Sprint copy test program, 1983, 2 folders (Box SR44)
    - Business Sprint disconnect study (SP Communication), 1982 (Box SR44)
    - Citiphone: An Initial Qualitative Evaluation, 1981 (Box SR44)
    - College market, 1981 (Box SR44)
    - Consumer research outline, undated (Box SR44)
    - Corporate identity study, 1983 (Box SR44)
    - Copy test of four Straight Talk commercials, 1983 (Box SR44)
    - Correspondence--Data Group, 1981 (Box SR44)
    - Correspondence--SP Communications, 1981-1982 (Box SR44)
    - Customer disconnect survey, 1983 (Box SR44)
    - Customer profile study, 1980-1983, 1-3 of 6 folders (Box SR44)
    - Customer profile study, 1980-1983, 4-6 of 6 folders (Box SR45)
    - Customer service research: Business and residential, 1982 (Box SR45)
    - Focus groups, 1982, 2 folders (Box SR45)
    - Home Sprint awareness image and attitude research, 1982 (Box SR45)
    - Home Sprint copy test of finished commercials, 1983, 2 folders (Box SR45)
    - Long distance telephone services, 1983 (Box SR45)
    - Market definition study, 1981 (Box SR45)
    - Market research recommendations, 1982 (Box SR46)
    - National directory study, 1982-1983 (Box SR46)
    - NSO caller follow-up study, 1982 (Box SR46)
    - Price vs. attribute study Stage 1, 1983, 2 folders (Box SR46)
    - Promotional test study, 1981 (Box SR46)
    - Proposals, 1981-1983 (Box SR46)
    - Residence customer profile study, 1983 (Box SR46)
    - Residential long distance strategic marketing, 1983 (Box SR46)
    - Sales analysis project, 1981-1982 (Box SR46)
    - Sales analysis report, 1981 (Box SR46)
    - Soft Touch III market test, 1983 (Box SR46)
    - SPC advertising effectiveness measurement program, 1981 (Box SR46)
    - Sprint service rejector study, 1981 (Box SR46)
    - Study examining the vitality of the Sprint name, 1982 (Box SR47)
    - Study of the Market for Discount long Distance Phone service in Honolulu, Hawaii, 1983, 2 folders (Box SR47)
    - Summary analysis of consumer positioning research, 1991 (Box SR47)
    - Summary of research, 1983 (Box SR47)
    - Syndicated study performer Q, 1991-1992 (Box SR47)
    - Television, 1980-1982 (Box SR47)
    - Television script, Clear Across America, 1986 (Box SR47)
    - Touch-tone penetration study, 1982 (Box SR47)
    - Ad claims, 1986 (Box SR47)
    - Communications briefing, 1984 (Box SR47)
    - Communications objectives, 1984 (Box SR47)
    - Holiday gift promotion, 1985 (Box SR47)
    - Summary of total code sales, 1983 (Box SR47)
    - T-Plan, 1983 (Box SR47)
    - Winter, 1986 (Box SR47)
  - Oversize
    - Advertising Academy poster, 1994 (Box SR48)
    - Articles, 1989-1996 (Box SR48)
    - Charts and statistical reports, 1982-1983 (Box SR48)
    - Competitive advertising--AT&T, 1989, 2 folders (Box SR48)
    - Competitive advertising--MCI, 1988 (Box SR48)
  - Restricted Materials
    - 1-800-ONE-Dime media issues, 1997 (Box SR49)
    - Brand investment group: First half 1996 advertising review, 1996 (Box SR49)
    - Brand vision and communications platform, 1997 (Box SR49)
    - Campaign architecture, 1997 (Box SR49)
    - Case study: El Salvador Sprint collect calling, 1995-present, 1997 (Box SR49)
    - Communications plan for 1997, 1996 (Box SR49)
    - Communications strategy for 1997, 1996, 2 folders (Box SR49)
    - Comparative marketing assessment, 1996 (Box SR49)
    - Competitive advertising fact book, 1996, 3 folders (Box SR50)
    - Competitive alert, 1996 (Box SR50)
    - Competitive analysis of telecommunications advertising in 1995, 1996 (Box SR50)
    - Competitive brand advertising, 1997 (Box SR50)
    - Consumer internet access, 1996, 2 folders (Box SR51)
    - Consumer internet access Day 1 brief, 1996 (Box SR51)
    - Consumer internet access 1996 fact book, 1997, 2 folders (Box SR51)
    - Consumer strategies, 1997 (Box SR51)
    - Corporation overview, 1996 (Box SR52)
    - Creative library dub catalog, 1997 (Box SR52)
    - CSG 1998 communications plan, 1997 (Box SR53)
    - CSG 1998 media plan recommendation, 1997 (Box SR53)
    - CSG business review, 1996 (Box SR53)
    - CSG business review document: General residential version, 1996 (Box SR53)
    - CSG communications strategy executive summary, 1996 (Box SR53)
    - CSG strategy related documents, 1996 (Box SR53)
    - Establishing a brand vision and communication plan, 1997 (Box SR54)
    - Evolution of Sprint Sense, 1997 (Box SR54)
    - Global business plan, 1996 (Box SR54)
    - Growing with the Business--roles and responsibilities (JWT Residential Team), 1997 (Box SR54)
    - Historical look at Sprint brand development, 1996 (Box SR54)
    - International access merchandising review, 1995, 1996 (Box SR54)
    - International competitive direct mail examples, 1996 (Box SR54)
    - Internet public access business case, 1996 (Box SR56)
    - Internet Passport, 1997 (Box SR57)
    - Organizing for local market opportunities, 1997, 3 folders (Box SR57)
    - Orientation for Sprint Ltd consumer and small business markets, 1998 (Box SR57)
    - Presentation: Integrated Advertising Support (NFL Sponsorship), 1996 (Box SR57)
    - Q4 1997 creative presentations: Short calls satisfaction, 1997 (Box SR57)
    - Selling Sprint in the new telecommunications market, 1996, 2 folders (Box SR57)
    - Sprint Advertising Academy, 1996, 2 folders (Box SR57)
    - Sprint brand identity standards, 1996 (Box SR57)
    - Sprint college client meeting, 1997 (Box SR58)
    - Sprint graphic timeline, 1997 (Box SR58)
    - Sprint Internet Passport, 1996 (Box SR58)
    - Sprint-Lucas Films strategic partnership, 1997 (Box SR58)
    - Sprint Sense brand review, 1997, 2 folders (Box SR58)
    - Sprint Sense evolution, 1997, 2 folders (Box SR58)
    - TCI Telephony new business meeting, 1996 (Box SR59)
  - Audiovisual--Originals
    - Bell Atlantic Commercials, 1987. Umatic. (Box SR60)
    - Building the Sprint Brand, 1998. VHS. (Box SR60)
    - Candice Bergen Retrospective, 1998. VHS. (Box SR60)
    - GTE Sprint Annual Report, 1984. Audiocassette. Goes with folder Annual Report (Box SR60)
    - Salute to Tom Weigman: Sprint All-Hands meeting, 1997. VHS. (Box SR60)
    - Sprint Historical Reel, 1982-1997. VHS. (Box SR60)
    - Sprint Historical Sampling, 1986-1997. VHS. (Box SR60)
    - Miscellaneous computer discs (5-inch floppy), 1984-1987. Goes with folder US Sprint Lexicon discs-Table of contents (Box SR60)
- Theodore Hamm Brewing Co., 1961-1973 and undated, 5 boxes
  [Contains billing, budget and project status reports; radio and television scripts, and a collection of competitor's beer cans and bottles.]
  - Billings, 1970-1972 (Box TH1)
  - Budget, 1967-1972, 3 folders (Box TH1)
  - Call reports, 1971-1972, 4 folders (Box TH1)
  - Conference reports, 1970-1972 (Box TH2)
  - Printed materials, 1961-1973 (Box TH2)
  - Project status reports, 1971-1972 (Box TH2)
  - Radio and television scripts master file, 1972 (Box TH2)
  - Competitors' beer cans and bottles, undated (Box TH3-5)
  - Sketches, undated: Moved to Small Files Series Oversize Box 55. (Box TH3-5, Folder 1)
- U.S. Playing Card Company, 1924-1966, 4 boxes
  [Contains correspondence, case histories, proofs, presentations, surveys, reports and scrapbooks related to the U.S. Playing Card Company account.]
  - Annual reports, 1940-1965 (Box UP 1)
  - General data, 1956 (Box UP 1)
  - Howard Henderson files
    - Case history, 1961 (Box UP 1)
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1938-1952, 4 folders (Box UP 1)
    - Data conference, 1934 (Box UP 1)
    - Data record, 1942 (Box UP 1)
    - Estimates and proofs, 1951-1952 (Box UP 1)
    - Memos and reproduction material, 1951-1952 (Box UP 1)
    - Presentation to U.S. government, 1942 (Box UP 1)
    - Review of activities, 1956 (Box UP 1)
    - Source book, 1952, 2 folders (Box UP 1)
  - Memoranda, 1963-1964 (Box UP 1)
  - Promotion material, 1954, 1957, 3 folders (Box UP 1)
  - Public relations program, 1966 (Box UP 1)
  - Publications, undated (Box UP 1)
  - Report to Executive Committee, 1936, 1938, 2 folders (Box UP 1)
  - Surveys,1934, 1944, 1951, 1957 and undated, 6 folders (Box UP 2)
  - William circaMcKeeham files
    - Annual reports, 1953-1956, 2 folders (Box UP 2)
    - Association of American Playing Card Manufacturers, 1953-1957, 7 folders (Box UP 2)
    - Correspondence and memoranda, 1953-1957, 9 folders (Box UP 2)
  - Scrapbooks
    - Scrapbook, circa 1924 (Box UP3)
    - Scrapbook inserts, circa 1924, 2 folders (Box UP3)
    - Scrapbook, circa 1935 (Box UP4)
    - Scrapbook inserts, circa 1935 (Box UP4)
- White Castle Restaurants, 1975-2006 and undated [RESTRICTED]
  - General Office Files
    - General, 1978-2000, 4 folders (Box WC1)
    - Account team, 1998 (Box WC1)
    - Articles on White Castle, 1975-1991 (Box WC1)
    - Brand kit #1, 1999 (Box WC1)
    - Competitive and industry articles, 1998 (Box WC1)
    - Direct mail template keylines, 2000-2001 (Box WC1)
    - Electronic media, 1995 (Box WC1)
    - Events
      - Event 2001--Air fresheners, 2001 (Box WC1)
      - Event recommendation, 1998 (Box WC1)
      - Events, 1995 (Box WC1)
      - Halloween, 1998 (Box WC1)
      - Snack attack event #5, 1998 (Box WC1)
    - Fact sheet, 1993 (Box WC1)
    - Financial
      - Budget breakdowns, 1995 (Box WC1)
      - Budget summary, 1998 (Box WC1)
      - Marketing budget, 1998 (Box WC1)
      - Quarterly post analysis, 1998 (Box WC1)
      - Sales, 1995 (Box WC1)
      - Storyboard pricing, undated (Box WC1)
    - Food shoot, 1999 (Box WC1)
    - Job openers/estimates, 1998 (Box WC1)
    - Kids Meal ESV's (electrostatic vinyl banner), 1998 (Box WC1)
    - Local Marketing and advertising planner, 1993-1994, 2 folders (Box WC2)
    - Location guides, 1996-2002, 2 folders (Box WC2)
    - Manager's quick reference sheet, undated (Box WC2)
    - Marketing calendars, 1992-1994 (Box WC2)
    - Media flights, 1995 (Box WC2)
    - Memoranda
      - Final presentation detail and checklist, 1993 (Box WC2)
      - Letter to J. Walter Thompson, 1993 (Box WC2)
      - No Visible competition memo, 1993 (Box WC2)
    - Merchandising
      - 80th anniversary pin, 2000 (Box WC2)
      - Air fresheners, 2001, 3 folders (Box WC2)
      - Calendar, 2000 (Box WC2)
      - Glow Coke cups, 2001 (Box WC2)
      - griddle glass stickers--New Jersey, 1998 (Box WC2)
      - Magnetic poetry summary report, 1998 (Box WC2)
      - Mint tin design, 1999 (Box WC2)
      - Promotional badges, 2006 and undated (Box WC2)
      - St. Louis lug-ons, 1998 (Box WC2)
    - Nutritional information, undated (Box WC2)
    - Omni Hotel meeting, 1993 (Box WC2)
    - Photographs, undated (Box WC2)
    - Planning
      - General, 1998 (Box WC2)
      - Advertising planning discussion, 1998 (Box WC2)
      - Brainstorming notes, 1999 and undated, 2 folders (Box WC2)
      - Media planning, 1998 (Box WC2)
    - Point of Crave (POC) campaign
      - Brainstorming, 1999 (Box WC2)
      - Breakfast, 2000 (Box WC2)
      - Combo Sack meal, 1999-2000 (Box WC3)
      - Crave Case, 2000-2001, 2 folders (Box WC3)
      - Crave Time cook-off, 2000 (Box WC3)
      - Gasoline card, 2001 (Box WC3)
      - Midnight Craver's kit, 1999 (Box WC3)
      - Official Point of Craving specifications guide, 1995 (Box WC3)
      - Recommendation, 1998 (Box WC3)
    - Presentations
      - 1999 planning, 1998 Aug. 20 (Box WC3)
      - Creative presentation: White Castle: What You Create, 1999 Dec. 9 (Box WC3)
      - Final presentation discussion guide and assignment, 1993 (Box WC3)
      - Marketing overview, 1990s-early 2000s (Box WC3)
    - Promotions
      - 30 Sack ESV, 1998 (Box WC3)
      - 80th anniversary video project, 2001 (Box WC3)
      - Chicago breakfast, 1998 (Box WC4)
      - Cravers contest, 2000 (Box WC4)
      - Gift certificate ESV, 2000 (Box WC4)
      - Griddle glass stickers, 1998 (Box WC4)
      - Grilled chicken, 1999 (Box WC4)
      - Keylines of the Tasty Trivia calender wings, 2000 (Box WC4)
      - Kids Eat Free, 1998 (Box WC4)
      - Promotional package, undated (Box WC4)
      - Sacks of Sides, 1998 (Box WC4)
      - What You Crave, 1995 (Box WC4)
    - Radio/Television
      - General, 1998-2000 and undated, 2 folders (Box WC4)
      - Comedy TV, 1999 (Box WC4)
      - Creative, 1998 (Box WC4)
      - Radio, 1998 (Box WC4)
      - Radio traffic, 1999 (Box WC4)
      - Rotation, 1998 (Box WC4)
      - Spanish scripts, 1998 (Box WC4)
      - Steam, 1998 (Box WC4)
    - Real Cheese logo, 1998 (Box WC4)
    - Recipes
      - Cookbooks and recipe books, 1996-2002 (Box WC4)
      - Cooking 'Em By The Sack, 1992 (Box WC4)
      - Recipe booklet, 1997-1998, 2 folders (Box WC4)
      - Recipe contest poster, 1997 (Box WC4)
    - Research
      - General, 1995 (Box WC4)
      - Awareness and attribute ranking studies, 1991-1993 (Box WC5)
      - Client reports, 1998 (Box WC5)
      - Consumer experience, 1999 (Box WC5)
      - Creative exploration, 1997, 2 folders (Box WC5)
    - Side cravings
      - General, 2000 (Box WC5)
      - Sample snacks, 1999-2001, 2 folders (Box WC5)
    - Specialty burgers, 1999 (Box WC5)
    - Sports tie-ins
      - Baseball, 2000 (Box WC5)
      - Pacers radio live reads (cups), 1996 (Box WC5)
    - Website
      - General, 1997 (Box WC5)
      - Articles, 1997 (Box WC5)
      - Graphics, 1997 (Box WC5)
      - Information, 1999 (Box WC5)
      - Update, 2000 (Box WC5)
    - Youth market, 1997 (Box WC5)
  - Artwork and Advertising Designs
    - ADVO art revised, 1998 (Box WC5)
    - ADVO hot, 1998 (Box WC5)
    - Coke card, 1999 (Box WC5)
    - Commercials
      - Scripts, 1999 (Box WC5)